[BUZZER PLAYS OVER SPEAKER]
(Sheldon:)All right, then,
my so-called friends have forsaken me.
(Sheldon:)So I guess it'll just be me
and my eyewitness.
(Penny:)Oh, balls.
(Sheldon:)Try to wear something appropriate.
It won't help my case if the judge...
...is busy trying to read the word "Juicy"
scrawled across your buttocks.
Penny. Penny.
(Sheldon:)Penny.
(Sheldon:)-That's just wrong.
-All right, let's go.
(Sheldon:)Wait. Hold on.
Before we get to the courthouse...
(Sheldon:)...I'd like to call on your skills
as an actress.
(Penny:)What is this?
(Sheldon:)I've taken the liberty of scripting
your appearance on the witness stand.
(Sheldon:)You're somewhat of a loose cannon.
(Sheldon:)Don't worry, it's written
in your vernacular. So shall we rehearse?
(Penny:)-Do I have a choice?
-Of course you have a choice.
(Sheldon:)Although we live in a deterministic
universe, each individual has free will.